all right boys today is a very special
day and the day has officially come
where I am buying my first
jet you made it right on
time SPO [__] now I'm saying J slow
it's
crazy I'm actually pretty excited
because I have flown on like 20 30 40
Jets but I've never actually been in the
process of buying my own I'm waiting for
Alejandro to pull up oh look he's here
he's BAS our host he's the one that's
going to get me the jet he's going to
park it right here when I do buy this
guy is a [__] legend for you guys
that don't know hey what you good for
you guys that don't know this is
Alejandro the legend tell them tell them
about yourself bro tell him something
like that something like that but every
time I get a call from this guy some
crazy [__] is happening and I [__]
love it honestly it's kind of why I love
what I do you know I get I get to do
crazy stuff with good people and about
to show you some stuff that I'm sure you
like this is my family's business and
this is an FBO as an FBO you know we
provide Fuel and ground services to
airplanes all these owners they pay rent
to keep their jet here regardless if
they fly or not they need a home where
to stay so he's a guy running the show
and he's got all the connections and
[__] so I'm like bro do you have the
opportunity to sell me a jet it's like
[__] yeah he has like 30 40 Jets here so
I'm like all right let's see what you
got h of course on a daily basis I even
get planes here that are brought here
just to get sold hey I need a space for
a month until the airplane gets sold so
something I'm about to show you right
now that's actually an airplane leaving
right now it's a hawker 800 which you
actually flown in it yeah let's go check
it out okay let's
[Music]
go this is a hawd 800 XP I want to show
you real quick all right let me
see sick so what so this is a 800 what x
this is a hawd 800 XP just like cars
also there's like different variances
throughout the years they come out with
different performances and improvements
this is a year 2000 depending on the
years they range between 1.5 million to
5 to 6 million this this this same jet
that same jet depending on you know how
many hours he got the maintenance
history that's that that what that's
what goes on behind when you're buying a
Jet you know you want to see the
pedigree and an inspection of what's
inside this yeah this is pretty and all
this but what really matters is the
engines and and the airframe corrosion
there's a lot that goes on one of the
main reasons why I really want to get a
jet is because bro I [__] hate
airports dude I airports are whack as
[__] bro like like going to the airp
well first of all you got to go through
traffic to get there you got to park in
the you know garage or through everybody
you have to go through the TSA [__]
and then your flight can get delayed you
got to rush cuz you can miss your flight
they close your Gates literally the
other day we were on our way to Columbia
on a commercial flight because we we
couldn't get the jet bro we we almost
missed our flight by 5 minutes the other
thing too which I know of You Realize by
this time flying private is addicting
super it's addicting it's a term flying
private is addicting once you start
flying you you get to see the the
comfort and the luxury and and the time
saving you get when when flying private
you see I see it on a daily basis you
know I see people that fly in we arrange
our rental C for them to go to their
meeting within one hour they ended up
their meeting you can live in the West
Coast and in one day even before on a 8
hour shift you can go to La and come
back on a meeting and you had a
successful you can be back home by 8:00
p.m. with your family whatever you're up
to so yeah that that's one of the main
reasons that I also want to get a jet
because I save like 2 three hours on
just [__] that I could be doing
something or let's say I'm not being
productive let's say I'm not working
right all that [__] like oh I have
to work those 2 three hours no it's more
of like I just want to [__] off those 2
three hours like instead of me being
struggling going through TSA and going
through the whole airport waiting for
the pilots waiting for the to take off I
could I rather just be chilling on my
phone talking to my boys like the time
that I save that I have to spend doing
that [__] just makes the flying
experience so much better that's that's
one of the other reasons and then three
it's just a [__] Flex bro you know
what I'm saying tell me about it I like
this one a lot but I want to see what
else you got for me let's see
[Music]
so this is a challenger 601 I believe
1984 doors are very scary with airplane
so they can come down real quickly it's
a big ass
[__] now we talking since it's an old
version of these jet this is a 1984
Challenger 601 this this plane actually
goes for around $2 million and actually
fun fact this airplane used to belong to
czecho Paris Formula 1 driver if you see
was it has some it used to have some
Mexican flag actually below that it's a
Mexican flight isn't that flag backwards
yes it is the mechanic in here is an
Argentinian guy so maybe that's why all
so as soon as you walk in you can see
how room it is yeah remember I'm 6'2 you
got to remember that never foret that
right so let me explain to you how I
plan to buy the jet because like I could
obviously buy one right now but I feel
like it'll be kind of like boring I feel
like I to have like a story and a reason
why so I'm going to start off this year
in 2025 with like a brand new Instagram
account I think I'm going to call it
trading or whatever and I'm going to
document myself turning like3 $4 million
account up until like 678 million and
when I hit that point I withdraw and
then I just buy the jet so I'm going to
be sharing you know how I did the 100 to
the mill of course to the m I'm going to
document the whole entire process me
taking the trades before during after
sharing it with people the Journey of me
taking the 3 four mil I haven't really
decided how much I'm going to start off
with yet I want to talk with you prices
how much is a jet maintenance so I know
how how much to start off with and
what's my goal going to be so I'm going
to document my whole journey basically
making the money to buy the jet it's
going to be [__] sick so you're
telling me you're actually just working
strictly on trading to buy a private jet
right now I have like five different
trading accounts but I'm going to have
one specifically where I'm going to
share with people of me risk it all to
to get your PJ I'm just going to trade
to buy a jet can you teach me how to
trade no no but I I like some [__] like
this bro you you go crazy here you know
you can actually do some crazy [__] very
roomy cevin like I said as being this
old it's it's within budget you know 2
million bucks but maintenance wise you
get to be aware these tend to break down
not very often but you got you got to
keep up with the airplane very very
often so that's something that you know
you got to keep aware of you get a call
hey the screen the screen broke 80k
besides the routinely maintenance which
you know around this airplane between
hanger Insurance maintenance you're
looking routine maintenance that that's
why I find like yeah maintenance
maintenance maintenance maintenance is
going to be yearly expense of everything
comes around 1.5 million 1.5 million on
just operating the jet for the whole
year no and actually flying actually
flying based on 300 hours which if you
think about it as a personal 300 hours
it's actually like the the average think
about what you're going to fly you also
have your year plans you you have your
Lo your set locations which we spoken
about it too you go to Dr you go to
Vegas you you got to think about also
the locations you're trying to go and
see if it makes sense cuz as I mentioned
before as well a $2 million jet smaller
might be a cheaper operation to run and
it's going to get you to the same places
so if I were to buy it in crypto you
guys stay crypto of
course it's a r house usually when I'm
in a room like this it's for cars and
like I I I know what I'm getting into
right explain to me what I'm getting
into with this right this is what you
should get into this is a 2003 Gold
Stream G4 SP this jet specifically goes
around $6 million I would say You' flown
on one of these so you know what it is
to fly on this you know it's very quiet
you know the comfort in this is almost
unmatchable golf streams are known for
how comfortable they are in terms of
capacity baggage performance operational
hour this tends to be within the best
airplanes in in that tier heavy jet to
operate so how much does it cost like
annually to operate all right so here's
a a breakdown like I said this breakdown
a screen breaking of $80,000 windshield
it's it's not here so this could be more
expensive yes absolutely 100% so that's
why I say this is based on routine
maintenance and based on on how much you
got to technically put into maintenance
on a yearly basis but when [__] breaks
down it's not here so that's kind of
what what you're going to think as well
first of all you need someone to fly the
airplane this is three Pilots three
Pilots fulltime is going to cost you
$450,000 around there the other way
which I've mentioned as well in the past
if it's a private airplane and you don't
want to have full-time Pilots you can
have a couple pilots on your insurance
where you pay them contract daily there
might be more cost on the long run
because you know if you fly with him for
a week you're paying a daily rate to him
regardless if he's flying or not you
know which at the end of the day you
know you could be paying him 10K a month
you can queeze him anytime you know so
that's something that rat for a G4 right
now and a contract pilot goes around
2,000 per day it's a G4 so you know it's
a big airplane you have to pay a
mechanic 60k a year just to be there yes
just like a pilot you know oh the
airplane broke you call your mechanic
you pay them daily for the labor so I I
don't have to have a flight attendant
either right knowing you I'm sure you
you know you're going to add it I have
20 flight attendant in my phone you know
you pay them on a daily rate and when
you fly with her or him I don't know if
you want to do him that definitely a h
okay okay so basically this would be the
cost to just keep it let's say at a
place like this exactly 12K a year a
year a year a year just to keep it in
the hanger the home base of theane even
if it goes 3 months out also that I
think that's a benefit of being here I
play around with that you got to do a
heavy maintenance there's maintenance
that puts down the airplane for 2 months
the shop you we found that it's the best
place it's in Georgia so you got to fly
the airplane there leave it for 2 months
for them to work but you're still paying
me the monthly home for the airplane
you're signing a year lease just like a
you like an apartment you you know you
signing a year lease or you can do month
to month where you're not attached but
usually that's higher what is this
navigation publication 16k what is that
that's unavoidable what is this
telecommunications $26,000 a year what
is that same it's just part of you know
all the softwares Pilots use so total
cost more or less it'll be around 1.2
million just to operate it during the
whole year give give or take we could
remove some things about a million
dollars no it's actually less this is
this is based on flying fake suspense
believe it or not just the airplane
parked and in good condition you're
looking at around $400,000 so that's
without moving it at all without moving
it at all fixed so with a full-time crew
and fixed cost yes you're looking at a
million dollars this is kind of a
average we put $4 here because that's my
price here around average I put these
because 50% of the time you're going to
fuel here fuel cost 430 G
per hour so it's $3,000 an hour $4,000
operational cost operational in a way in
a way you know on top of these you got
to add the fees where you land you know
all that but technically this this
number is hard to to get to nowadays but
this is exactly what what it should be
flying private is such a privilege I
think it's the most luxurious and
expensive service in the world fly
private in the world for sure more than
chartering a yacht a round trip to Japan
is going to cost you over $200,000 you
break down those
$200,000 per hours flown so you're
spending 40 hours on the jet charging a
super yacht a mega yacht $1 15 footer
will cost you $300,000 a week and you're
there 247 and you're there for a whole
week instead of just 40 hours sitting on
a plane you're flying it's not on a
super yet you're you can do whatever
you're actually vacation you're actually
having fun within those
$300,000 of what you're paying on a week
on a Yu let me ask you something aside
from your goal of buying a private jet
this year what else are you up to well
we want to streak another Super Bowl you
know we want to do that again so if you
do that you know I have the jet ready so
when you guys get the [__] out hey turn
on the turn on the engine boom we're out
nah no we'll probably do that but a real
goal is I want to get my students
collectively to make $5 million in
trading this year last year they did
like 1.2 1.5 million like all the
students together copy my trades and
with the strategy but in 20125 I want to
document every single Trader that goes
into my community from Level Z to 100 so
they make trading and they add to this
whole entire chart overall so you keep
up with your students where they tell
you how much they're making and how much
their traes are hitting yeah so we have
a tracking sheet where every single
person that makes profit they post it in
our school community and inside that
section we add it every single day and
we put it to like you know like this
like ticker that just adds every single
day it just like adds oh [__] so like
there's days that we can add $20,000
there's days where we can add $100,000
how many trades are done between your
students yeah like we all take the same
trade but there's like 15,000 students
you know so like but and and then the
other thing is not not all students
report the trades so like that's
something we're going to double down
this year like we're going to force
everybody to report the trades just
getting people to be part more of the
community as including to getting
students to make $5 million this year
also I'm going to write a book I'm going
to write a trading book bro oh [__] you
got [__] Shakespeare over here yeah
we got we got some [__] cooking bro we
we have an interesting journey ahead of
us like documenting this whole entire
account we're going to literally try and
make it as transparent as we possibly
can bro literally like cuz the goal is
to show people you just need some type
of money and whatever goal you want to
have let's say you want to buy a car
that you start up with a certain amount
of money you follow a trading plan and
with the same trading profits you can
buy that exact thing we're just taking
an up a notch and buying [__]
J one of my main goals to do this year
as well well in 2025 is to build my own
dream house now I don't know if this is
because it's a Cuban tradition or it's
like an American Dream but I've always
had a dream to build my own house like
literally buy a piece of dirt like this
and buy it so you notice this they
already cut it price from a million so
they had it at 2.8 now it's at 1.8
million but I get a total of 5 acres and
right now there's like like a little
shitty house on it you guys can see this
is like the full 5 acre property this is
basically one of the little houses that
it has back there and this is one of the
sheds one of I guess where like the
horses and they keep the stuff but like
for me building the dream house has
always been my goal because I can make
it exactly how I want and I've never
believed in buying an old house and
remodeling it because you never actually
build it how you want you're kind of
just getting like a like an ugly girl
and then you're kind of just putting
makeup on it like it's just better to
just like make your own you want to make
it the whole thing you get what I'm
saying so check it so look this house
actually has like I guess horses and all
this and I do plan to have horses in my
house but not on this old shitty Barn
respectfully but if you look at the
property up from the top you can see all
the space laid out right here so if you
notice it has a lake to the right of it
as well so I can build a humongous house
right here and then right here we can
have a pool we can have a big basketball
tennis court right here here we can have
a guest house back over here have a koi
pond and over here we can have the gym
and then like another little workout
area and then we have a little bridge to
the canal if we want to go fish or throw
the jet ski in there we could do it
basically like my own full compound I
don't have to leave for anything right
now I live in an acre and a half almost
this is 5 Acres so this is literally
almost three times what I have right now
and it gives me plenty of space my house
would literally be all of this right
here it' be about 15,000 square ft
around 10 bathrooms and like 12 bedrooms
three stories and the front here would
be the whole entire house big driveway
again pool tennis court Koi pond gym and
then a bridge over here to the side
everything like having it on a corner
lot how this one is is perfect and the
best way to do it is to buy one of these
old shitty houses we come in we break it
down build something up new and
truthfully it's what I've always wanted
to do along with buying my own Jet and
making a book is something that I very
recently got passionate about not a big
reader but I am a big Storyteller I like
explaining things to people and I I
think I am great at expressing myself
and making sure that the message get
sent across and if I can put that on an
actual book I feel like it'd be great
because I'm developing this new talent
that I can potentially take on to the
Future and see where that goes and then
truthfully making my students make $5
million this year is going to be
absolutely lit along with me making $15
million this year it's kind of like my
overall goals that I'm going to work for
every single day in 2025 buying my jet
building my Dreamhouse creating my book
student results of 5 million and my
results of 15 million everything else
that I do aside from that is just a
little sprinkle on top but my whole
entire 2025 is going to be devoted
solely and uniquely on that right there
so it's going to be very interesting
year if you guys are not subscribed to
the channel make sure you guys hit that
subscribe button because trust me we did
a lot of crazy [__] in 2024 and we are
not slowing down in 2025 I'll see you
guys then hit the Subscribe button set
and forgets and I'll see you guys later
and this is not my dream house right now
this house that I'm in right now I love
it because I have full acre basketball
court gym chickens goats back there it's
not my dream house and I already have my
own plao tree but my [__] plao trees
keep breaking we're on to our last blat
tree this is straight from the Alex G
set forget
home well honestly I don't think I don't
think this is ready
yet so good we have our gym which is
finally finished our second office and
back over here is we're going to have
our goats and our chickens oh and my
barber shop is going to beew but over
here chickens will be over there my
goats all along here wait until I do my
dream house